(Amy:)Can you believe it's been
five years since our first date?
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Sheldon:)Do you think I should start
watching The Flash TV show?
(Amy:)That's what
you're thinking about?
(Sheldon:)Well, one of the things.
(Amy:)Are any of them me?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
I thought, "I can't decide
"if I should watch
The Flash TV show.
I know, I'll ask Amy."
(Sheldon:)Anyway...
(Amy:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)You're right, you did
kind of kill the mood.
(Amy:)I didn't kill anything.
(Amy:)You did, talking about
your stupid TV show.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Starting to watch a television
show that might run for years
(Sheldon:)isn't a decision
to take lightly.
(Sheldon:)I'm wrestling with
(Sheldon:)a big commitment issue here.
(Amy:)Really?
(Amy:)That's the commitment issue
you're wrestling with?
(Amy:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)do you understand the irony
(Amy:)of your fixation on a man
with super speed,
(Amy:)while after five years
all I can get out of you
(Amy:)is a distracted make-out session
on a couch?
(Sheldon:)Irony's not really
my strong suit.
(Sheldon:)But I have been getting better
with sarcasm,
(Sheldon:)if you want to give that a try.
(sarcastically):
Oh, sure, I'd love to.
(Sheldon:)Whenever you're ready.